# **Paulius Kancleris**

Dagenham, London

M: 07599089768 E: kanclerispaul@gmail.com

Portfolio: paul-kanc.github.io LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/paul-kanc/

### **Profile**

Paulius is a a highly motivated Computer Science graduate with hands-on experience in both technical and client-facing roles. Currently working as a Technical Advisor at Alcove, he configures care technology devices, troubleshoots issues, and supports customers directly - combining technical precision with strong interpersonal skills. Paulius' interest in building custom computers and exploring emerging technologies continues to strengthen his knowledge, contributing to his personal and professional development.

#### **Education**

### BSc Computer Science with Honours - City, University of London

2020-2023

Grade: Class 1

• Modules: Concurrency, Object-Oriented Design, Theory of Computation, Data Structures, Al...

### BTEC & AS-Level - Havering Sixth Form College

2018-2020

BTEC: ICT Extended Diploma (D\*D\*D\*)

AS-Level: Maths (A)

### GCSEs - Anglo European School

2013-2018

10 subjects, grades 4-6, C, B, including Maths and English

## **IT Skills & Projects**

**Languages:** Python, Java, Visual Basic, Dax, Haskell, C++

Databases and Web Development: HTML, PHP, CSS, JavaScript, MySQL

Programmes and Software Packages: VS Code, Microsoft Office, Power BI, IntelliJ IDEA, Visual Paradigm

**Projects:** Examples can be found in my <u>online portfolio</u>

# **Work Experience**

#### **Alcove Technical Advisor**

November 2024 - ONGOING

- Alcove is a care technology company that provides devices ensuring swift emergency response.
- Paulius acts as the primary point of contact for customers, ensuring their personal details are correctly registered across all relevant portals and devices.
- Installs devices and troubleshoot technical issues, ensuring optimal performance and usability for each customer.
- Strengthened interpersonal skills by adapting explanations to suit the needs of diverse customers.
- Developed strong time management skills by balancing technical installations, customer support, and administrative tasks in a fast-paced, understaffed environment.

### **Tesco Warehouse Operations Technician**

### August 2023 – November 2024

- Distributed food from pallets arriving to the warehouse into aisles, each with a designated shop destination.
- Held detailed knowledge of warehouse equipment allowing completion of specialised tasks upon request.
- Enhanced ability to thrive in a fast-paced environment by meeting strict performance targets.
- Improved team working skills as everyone contributes towards maintaining each others efficient operations.

#### **Additional Skills and Information**

Languages: Lithuanian (fluent), English (fluent)

**Hardware:** Actively enhances his technical expertise by designing and assembling computers.

**Sports:** Strong interest in basketball and follows the NBA.

**Gaming:** Mainly online games such as Call of Duty, Rocket League and Valorant.